girlgamezone.com 2011-05-04

# Privacy Policy - www.girlgamezone.com

****

**Privacy Policy for[www.girlgamezone.com](http://www.girlgamezone.com/) **

At www.girlgamezone.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. We are committed to protecting your privacy and we acknowledge that you may have concerns regarding the use of your personal information.This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.girlgamezone.com and how it is used. 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [**debra@girlgamezone.com**](mailto:debra@girlgamezone.com) ****

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, **www.girlgamezone.com** makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.The information we collect is only used to improve the content, or layout of our Web pages, and technical upkeep of our site.. If choosing to register with our games arcade,  you will be asked to enter a username and an e-mail address. **Registration however, is not mandatory,** so you may play games without registering, and thus remain anonymous.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Some of our advertising partners may use **cookies and web beacons** on our site to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**Our advertising partners include .......**

 **Google Adsense -** **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

The **Google Advertising Cookie** is also called the **DoubleClick DART**

-:: **Google** , as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on **www.girlgamezone.com.  
** .:: **Google's** use of the **DART cookie** enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to **www.girlgamezone.com** and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users **may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by** visiting the **Google ad and content network privacy policy** at the following URL -[ ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

While using **Google Advertising** on our site, we have deliberately take care to screen and opt out of those categories of advertising which we feel may be particularly unsuitable for younger viewers under 13. However, we advise and recommend parental support to those younger age groups when visiting our site, as we are unable to guarantee that all our ads and external links will be completely appropriate for younger age groups.    
 ****

 **Amazon.com**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.girlgamezone.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

**www.girlgamezone.com** has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **www.girlgamezone.com's** privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

**If you wish to disable cookies** , you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

### External Sites & Third party links 

As one of Girlgamezones functions is to service as an online games directory, our website does include many external links to other websites, and we may also sometimes include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site  welcome any feedback about these sites. Girlgamezone is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information. 

**Child Safety**

Girlgamezone tries hard to ensure that our website is overall safe, family-friendly viewing with links to good quality and safe sites. However, as our website provides information and thousands of links to external sites for a wide ranging age group, people with younger children, may wish to supervise them whilst they browsing our site. 

If you have any further concerns about how to protect your child's safety, please check Safety Advice websites for kids, or you may this link helpful:<http://www.google.co.uk/familysafety/>

 **Parental Consent**

For any personal information that we collect from children, parents and guardians may request information on the type of data being collected, view their child’s information, and, if they choose, prohibit us from making further use of their child’s information. We will not provide personal information collected from children to third parties except when we believe that doing so is required by law, may be necessary to protect a person’s property, rights, or safety, or to investigate a potential violation of law, or in the event of a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale.
